DIBBO DAS

Graphics Designer and Video Editor

CONTACTS



+8801871126615



Dibbodasavi@gmail.com



<u>Dibbodasavi</u>



@Dibbodasavi



www.dibbodasavi.tech



Graphic Portfolio

EDUCATION

B.Sc. in Textile Engineering

Chittagong Textile

Engineering College

(2019-2023)

SKILLS

Content Marketing

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere Pro

About Me

For more than five exciting years I have been heavily involved in marketing, In addition to this, my passion for graphic design and video editing is the main stronghold that allows me to create visually stunning stories. I have worked with clients from all over the world, I thrive on bringing highly moving ideas to life.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Upwork marketplace

May 2019 - July 2022

Video Editor And Marketing Coordinator

> (Contractual-Remote) Ayn Rand Institute (ARI)

May 2023 — Sep 2023

Regional Coordinator Of Design And Marketing (Remote)

Students For Liberty

Apr 2023 - Present

VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCE

COMMITTEE MEMBER

(Promotion and Marketing) Volunteers For Bangladesh

July 2020 - Feb 2022

HEAD OF MARKETING AND PUBLIC RELATIONS

SAFE Teen

April 2021 - Feb 2022

SKILLS

Canva

Web Design WordPress **Audio Editing** Social Media Management Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft Powerpoint INTERESTS Technology Travel Photography Designing Drawing Music Flute

EXPERIENCE

CREATIVE ASSOCIATE

(Design) Boiferi

Feb 2020 - Jan 2021

■ ASSISTANT DIRECTOR OF PROMOTION AND PUBLIC RELATIONS

HULT Prize at CTEC
July 2020 - Dec 2020

EXAM CONTROLLER &CAMPUS AMBASSADOR

ENGLISH OLYMPIAD

JULY 2020 - DEC 2022

DEPUTY DIVISIONAL COORDINATOR

SERAC BANGLADESH

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

BATTALION SERGEANT MAJOR (BSM)

Bangladesh National

Cadet Corps (BNCC) Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

AWARDS& ACHIEVEMENTS

- Attended Top Leadership Retreat, Kathmandu, Nepal 2022 as a top performer of the year from Students For Liberty.
- Textile talent hunt (19-20): Secured 9th Position in Chittagong Division.
- ☐ Attended **Asia Top Leadership Retreat, Malaysia 2023** as a top performer of the year from Students For Liberty.